chennai365.com 2018-05-03

# Chennai365 | Privacy Policy | Chennai365

Chennai365 values the privacy of our visitors and our members and takes many steps to protect their privacy. By visiting Chennai365’s website, or using any of our services, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Statement.

 **What this Privacy Statement Covers**

This Privacy Statement covers Chennai365’s treatment of personally identifiable information (â€œPersonal Information??) that Chennai365 gathers when you access Chennai365 Sites. This Privacy Statement does not apply to the use of your Personal Information by third parties that Chennai365 does not own or control, or to individuals that Chennai365 does not control or manage.

 **Links to Other Sites**

Chennai365 Sites contains links to blogs and other websites that are not owned or controlled by Chennai365. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of such other sites.

 **Information Collection & Use**

Chennai365 is the sole owner of information collected on Chennai365 Sites. We do not share or sell your information with anyone without your authorization or consent in ways different from what is disclosed in this Privacy Statement.

 **Registration**

Chennai365 may provide features exclusively to its members(in future). Our registration process requires you to provide Chennai365 with a valid email address as well as a username. Optional information such as your first and last name, year of birth, zip code, and country of residence helps Chennai365 have a better understanding of its visitors and members. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of special features offered only to our members.

 **Minor’s Privacy**

We do not collect or maintain information on Chennai365 Sites from those people we actually know are under 13 years old, and no part of any Chennai365 Site is structured to attract anyone under 13 years old.

 **Surveys or Contests**

We may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on Chennai365 Sites. If you participate we will request certain Personal Information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code).

We only use this information internally to determine eligibility, notify contest winners, and to measure the success of our efforts.

 **Aggregate Information**

We DO NOT share any aggregated demographic information about our visitors and the world of weblogs with our partners and advertisers.

We may employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Examples of such services include sending email, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, and providing customer service

We reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to (1) comply with the law; (2) enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; (3) or protect the rights, property or safety of Chennai365, our employees, our users, or others.

 **Security and Confidentiality**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

Users of the Chennai365 Sites are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require an outside party.

We gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, requested pages, operating system, and the time and date your browser requested our pages. We use this information, which does not identify individual visitors, to analyze trends, to administer the Chennai365 Sites, to track visitor movements around the Chennai365 Sites and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this collected data to Personal Information.

 **Cookies**

We store a small text file called a cookie on your computer to track session data and persist your login (if needed) for your convenience. A session cookie expires when you exit your browser. A persistent cookie stays on your computer until it is deleted. You can remove persistent cookies by following the directions provided in your browserâ€™s â€œhelpâ€ files.

If you reject cookies you may still use the Chennai365 Sites.

Some of our advertisers may use cookies on the Chennai365 Sites. We have no access or control over these cookies. This Privacy Statement covers the use of cookies by Chennai365 only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

The use of cookies and/or web beacons to collect data is used in the ad serving process. We do not have access to this data. Google uses the DART cookie to serve ads to our users based on their previous visits to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

 **Third Party Advertisers**

The advertisements appearing on Chennai365 are delivered by a third party. For information about our advertising partner, please visit their website through the link included in the presentation of the advertisements on the Chennai365 Sites.

 **Business Transitions**

In the event Chennai365 goes through a business transition such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Chennai365 may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Statement. You hereby consent to Chennai365 sharing your Personal Information under the above circumstances. Chennai365 will contact you at the email address you provided at registration to communicate such transfer. We will also place a prominent notice on the Chennai365 home page for 30 days after such transfer of your Personal Information.

 **Changes in this Privacy Statement**

This Privacy Statement is a living document. We will modify this document as we add new features to Chennai365. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Statement at any time. If we make material changes to our privacy policy we will post those changes to this Privacy Statement, the Chennai365.com homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

 **Contact Us**

If you have any questions, issues, concerns or suggestions regarding our privacy policy please contact us at info at Chennai365.com
